She is Amina and she fears nobody.
Amina is a war, history, drama film directed by Izu Ojukwu.
In 16th-century Zazzau, now Zaria, Nigeria, Amina must utilize her
military skills and tactics to defend her family's kingdom.
Based on a true story.
Amina, played by Lucy Ameh.
Danjuma, played by Ali Nuhu.
Zumbura, played by Clarion Chukwurah-Abiola.
Sarki, played by Chris Gbakann.
Madaki, played by Ibrahim Mijinyawa.
Zaria, played by Ummi Mohammed.
Amina is a 2021 Nigerian action drama film directed by Izu Ojukwu.
It is based on the story of the life of 16th century
Zazzau empire warrior Queen Amina.
Amina premiered on Netflix on November 4, 2021.
The film got the most nominations at Africa Magic Viewers' Choice Awards, 2022.
The film explores themes of africa, gore,
biography, based on true story, nigeria.
The tone is emotional.